30 Reasons to do
------------------------

A description of the project to use for the meta page description. This will be picked up by google and by facebook if peeps share the url

An example of the disclaimer language we were discussing needed to be at the bottom of every page. Is this still the case, or is it covered by the intermediate page that comes up when you download a poster? If it's still the case, does it have to be physically there on every page or is a persistent link to a "Terms" page what we need? 

IE8 fixes
- Convert to desktop layout?


IE7
- Passable. Missing right padding on things, prob because of border box.
- Not worth fixing


30 Reasons Done
-----------------------------
make thumbnails align center (or margin auto) so on in-between widths they are always behind their reason number

content container bottom padding x 2 ?

firefox outlines on hover messed up. use borders instead? look into this. on hover they expand to enclose the box shadow

center footer on narrow widths

change navigation menu hover to black? NO

change about section icon to ?

adjust spacing between top nav icons and labels

change navigation menu header color to black

Add reason number line

Grid widths on about page? 50/50 ok?

Footer share buttons taller on small/all screens?

Menu link more clearspace on iphone layouts
 - Remove "Menu" text?
 - Push link up into gap above title?

Shrink margin below header on iphone layouts

h1 smaller on iphone vertical layout

Inline the form button

Nbsp's in sign up header. 

Also, put new markup on other pages.

Change the blue to pass AA contrast ratios?

Permalink on homepage post and today's post?

Larger captions on phone layouts? NO

large version of poster max-width: 640px

Favicons, iOS icons

Add 1px border to right and bottom of tombstone for no box shadow browsers

Printer icon for download button instead?

Top-of-page social icons it is. I'll add as I make some of the last set of changes this weekend. I think they will fit, but in case not, I might need to drop the "Today's Reason" link in the main nav, leaving it Home, All Reasons and About. Do you think that would be bad?

30 days, 30 posters. 30 Reasons to re-elect President Obama on November 6th.

IE8 fixes
- Pagination fix? Can't see names and numbers are centered. Might be because of the way I'm using keywords here instead of like I do everywhere else? Check this. The "previous" word showed up in IE7 so there's a clue.
- Image centering? Center the large poster image like the thumbnails do
- Show the "Menu" word on IE8 layout? Since it's using mobile layout the "Menu" word doesn't show even though it has room

Facebook social graph meta stuff to other pages besides index.


